WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
What happened?
What happened next?
Can you guess who it is?
Someone who's close to you
and knows you…
The waveform analysis indicates
a woman in her twenties.
Compare it with 406.
See how much they match in percentage.
Up to two decimal places.
EPISODE 6
Why…
were we lying on the floor together
last night?
What? What is it?
What is it?
Tell me if something happened.
Should I tell you everything honestly?
Honest…
"Tell you everything honestly"?
PARK DO-JAE
Yes?
Mr. Paik.
What happened?
Your phone was off. I was worried.
I'm sorry.
It just happened.
As for the favor I asked for yesterday?
Did you not see it?
I sent you a text last night.
But you never responded.
It's a 99.99% match.
I made a summary of all the events so far.
From the first threatening call
to the recent incident
at the nursing home.
I came to one conclusion.
The caller, 406, isn't involved
in the kidnapping, explosion,
and nursing home incident.
There's someone else.
I know that.
They're not accomplices.
You have an idea who 406 might be,
don't you?
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you right now.
For now, let's find the connection
between him and 406 and break it.
After that…
Are you okay?
You don't look well.
I'm fine.
Yes, sir.
If you need anything--
No.
I'm not okay.
You see,
I thought
I'd controlled situations perfectly
and made better judgments than anyone.
I thought I had lived meticulously
not to fall into any traps.
But…
why didn't I know?
When I think back,
there were more than a few hints.
Maybe I just ignored them.
I firmly believed it couldn't be true,
desperately hoping it wasn't.
But I shouldn't have done that.
I should've at least prepared myself.
If I had,
I wouldn't be at a loss for what to do.
You have until tomorrow to decide.
Or we can settle for two billion won.
You have until tomorrow.
It's not like you married her for love.
You don't even love her now.
If it's going to be like that,
just leave her.
THE SEVENTH CALL
Then why did you treat her
like she was invisible?
THE THIRD CALL
It's Hong Hee-joo's…
thigh.
You're supposed to be her husband.
Didn't you know
Hee-joo has a unique mole on her thigh?
How could you not know?
Were you just not interested? Or…
have you never seen her naked?
Enough.
It grew longer as I wrote.
100 QUESTIONS, 100 ANSWERS
Wait. I forgot one.
LIES, ANGER, HATRED,
MISUNDERSTANDING, FORGIVENESS
What's the sign language
for forgiveness?
What about "I forgive your wrongdoings"?
It's difficult.
Forgiveness.
Let's end today's class here.
YOU DIDN'T TEXT BACK,
SO I'M TEXTING AGAIN. LET'S MEET UP TODAY.
SIGN LANGUAGE
The pre-candidate registration
for the 21st presidential election,
which will be held in March next year,
will begin next week.
Sir.
It's about the task
you asked me to check regularly.
Regarding Chairman Hong Il-gyeong's
eldest daughter, Hong In-a.
Honey.
Chairman Hong's eldest daughter
is back in Korea.
So what?
What do you mean?
You should meet with her.
And ask her why she caused that mess.
No, before that, see if we can control…
Are you drinking?
Are you drunk?
Can't I be drunk?
On a day like today?
What's today?
What is it?
A day no one can remember.
A day that shouldn't be remembered.
That's what your father decided.
So what?
Why? Must you pretend to care?
Would that ease your guilt a little?
Don't make me laugh.
Twenty years ago today,
both you and I know how we really felt!
What?
A sense of freedom.
IS IT IMPOSSIBLE
TO CHANGE INNATE TEMPERAMENT?
Goodness.
You must be In-a.
How dare you touch me
with your filthy hands?
Hee-joo.
How have you been?
Do you remember?
We'd visit the aquarium often as kids.
It felt like all the sounds
in the world disappeared
when I stared into the water like this.
It made me feel at peace.
Let's see the mermaid show you like.
It starts soon.
Isn't it amazing?
Hearing me chattering like this.
I must've been lucky.
The surgery was a success.
No surgery could fix me when I was young.
But, Hee-joo…
why are you still the same?
You can talk now.
You don't need to keep quiet.
You knew?
Yeah.
You didn't speak…
because of me.
I know.
I did a terrible thing to you.
I know it was awful of me,
but I didn't want to fall apart alone.
I needed someone to be miserable
with me.
Hee-joo.
So what?
Now that you're okay,
are you allowing me to speak?
No, that's not up to you.
I'll decide it.
I won't let you interfere
in my life anymore.
You don't know what I'm saying, do you?
It doesn't matter.
I'll say what I want,
just like what you're doing.
THE LITTLE MERMAID'S MYSTERIOUS ADVENTURE
I don't like The Little Mermaid.
I hate her.
IN-A
Hee-joo.
I needed to tell you something today.
Do you think you know Paik Sa-eon well?
Before the wedding,
I didn't dump you on him.
He asked for you.
In return for letting me go,
he needed a connection to our family,
so he took you hostage.
I came to one conclusion.
The caller, 406, isn't involved
in the kidnapping, explosion,
and nursing home incident.
There's someone else.
It's just…
My phone's missing.
Why is he looking for that here?
CALLS
PAIK SA-EON
Wait.
What's this?
So Hee-joo was…
into this kind of thing?
Did I…
I mean,
did we…
by any chance…
I must be insane.
How did you know?
About what?
That I've been thinking about you
all day long.
We spoke on the phone every day.
But there are still so many things
I don't know about you.
So now I want to know more.
Then…
how about we each
ask a question and answer?
Sounds good.
However, from this moment on,
we'll only speak the truth.
That's what I want.
Go ahead.
The day before the wedding,
you said you met In-a and made a deal.
Was the deal about Hong Hee-joo?
Yes.
It's my turn.
What? My question isn't over yet.
I answered, so it's over.
Think carefully next time before you ask.
It's my turn.
Is Hong Hee-joo being threatened
right now?
Why do you think she's being threatened?
406, you kidnapped Hee-joo
and even attacked her father.
You're completely insane.
Hee-joo would never side
with someone like you.
She's being threatened,
but also not, okay?
It's my turn now.
Did you take Hong Hee-joo hostage
in exchange for letting Hong In-a
go free from the arranged marriage?
Who told you that?
Seeing how you're asking that,
I guess it's true.
It's true.
I…
often have nightmares.
I had them more often as a kid.
I will
help you.
I will be with you.
It's okay.
What calmed me down every time…
were the gestures of the girl next door
who practiced sign language every night.
But that girl
had no one
to rely on, anywhere.
Because to her,
Chairman Hong's house was a prison.
I wanted to help her escape.
Hoping that she could
leave that house and live freely.
But I never imagined…
that I would become…
Hee-joo's new prison.
Prison?
A married life with me
after leaving that house
must've felt like a prison to her.
That must be why she got mixed up
with some crazy person
in order to divorce me, right?
It's my turn now.
Does Hong Hee-joo…
still want a divorce?
Answer me, 406.
Isn't that what you kept saying?
To let Hee-joo go
and return things to the way they were.
To let go of her.
She didn't want
to get her hopes up anymore.
"Someday,
things will change."
"It'll get better."
She waited and hoped for three years.
If you let her go,
she thought she wouldn't get hurt
or be disappointed anymore.
That's what Hong Hee-joo thought.
By any chance,
does Hee-joo want…
SINCERITY
sincerity,
attention,
understanding,
and affection?
Is that what she wants?
What are you saying? What I'm saying--
I can give that to her.
I can give her everything.
If that's what Hee-joo wants,
I'll give as much as she needs.
Why do you suddenly want to do that?
You didn't care whether I lived or died,
or whether I was by your side, until now.
From the very start,
this wasn't a marriage Hee-joo wanted.
I kept her by my side as a hostage,
thinking that someday…
I'd have to let her go.
Is that why you were so cruel?
So you wouldn't get attached?
But if that's what Hee-joo wants,
it changes things.
Then promise me.
If I make an effort
and we can change,
promise you'll never make this call again.
That depends on how you act.
Oh, my, ma'am.
You look so young and beautiful today.
Of course.
My age may increase,
but my skirt length shouldn't.
Of course.
Can't you dress a bit younger too?
Why should I have to struggle
to look younger?
You're right.
It wouldn't suit you.
You already have a gorgeous charm
about you.
Okay, then.
Get in. Good luck today.
Let's go. Okay.
How much is Spokesperson Paik asking for?
What?
What's his price?
Good luck with the negotiation.
Between parents and children,
there should be
some playful give-and-take.
I don't know.
Don't you know as well as I do?
Getting a stubborn child to listen
is harder than practicing discipline.
Your eldest daughter.
Do you know how she's doing?
Why would you suddenly bring her up?
She comes to mind lately.
I wonder how she's doing.
- Are you ready for this?
- I've never been to a retreat before.
- I've organized this well.
- I am a little nervous.
Is that like your security pillow?
So only Mr. Paik and Mr. Park
aren't here yet?
- Should I call them?
- Nah.
What? What's that?
What is that?
THANK YOU, SPOKESPERSON'S TEAM
WHEEL LUNCHBOX
TO THE SPOKESPERSON'S TEAM, THANK YOU
Let's go.
The staff from the spokesperson's office?
- Yes.
- The lunchboxes have arrived.
- Thank you.
- Here you go.
Pass these out.
Take that.
Thank you.
Goodness.
- Do you have mine?
- Goodness.
Look at the hearts.
"An office full of love."
Is that what this is, Mr. Kang?
It wasn't me. I didn't order these.
Who sent these?
I don't know.
Is everyone here?
- Hello.
The lunchboxes came too.
Wait, did you order these, sir?
- Let's go.
- Wait…
- What?
- What's going on?
- Let… Let's go.
- What?
Look at this heart.
I didn't know
he'd prepare lunchboxes for us.
Is this seat taken?
Do you want one?
I get…
carsick.
Doesn't it get worse
if you sit in the back?
Right. Then why don't you sit there?
I think I'll leave my things here.
I see.
Then would you like to sit here?
Thank you.
Coffee…
isn't good on an empty stomach, Ms. Hong.
Proof?
Are we cops or something?
How can we find proof?
A witness?
There's no proof.
How would we find a witness?
Not to mention,
these kids don't have a family.
It's in the development stage.
If we keep digging…
Hello?
Mr. Han?
What?
He just hung up on me.
Do they want to toss it?
- Well…
- "If the NeoTuber's story is fake,
will you take responsibility?"
Why would I take responsibility?
You have to.
Why are you helping so enthusiastically?
Because…
Why are you buying so much?
It's not that much.
At least for hungry little ones
whose stomachs can never be filled.
I'm a huge fan of hers!
I need to get her autograph.
I don't believe it.
Thank you so much.
- Hello!
- Cool.
Thank you.
Are you Dr. Sang-woo's girlfriend?
What?
Want to see his dark past?
If you still like him after,
it's real love.
No, wait.
I'm not Dr. Sang-woo's girlfriend.
Guys, let's eat!
Be careful.
Let's eat.
No, you can't look!
Wait! Hey!
Hey! This isn't right.
This picture…
I heard the kids started disappearing
around this time.
This was before you came here.
Do you know anything?
No, I don't.
Did any of the birth parents come back
later on?
So, the missing kids
had no family searching for them
and no one to remember them all this time.
Shin Yeong-seok liked to play marbles,
and he was so competitive.
Lee Jin-yeong liked cars.
Park Min-woo. He was so…
Such a troublemaker.
I remember them.
These three.
That's strange.
I heard
that four kids disappeared.
There's one more?
Yes, here.
One of the twin brothers.
CHANGE OF PLAN. TODAY'S D-DAY.
Hey, honey.
No, I wasn't sleeping.
Is it hard on your own?
Sorry, I couldn't go.
What?
Yeah.
I love you,
my ultimate love in the universe!
Park Eun-yeong, I love you so much!
I apologize.
How do you do that?
Excuse me?
What you just did.
"I love you,
ultimate love in the universe."
You're good at that.
You know,
it's only hard at first,
but it gets easier to do.
Think of it as adding a little flavor
to the affection you usually show.
Say it with a kiss.
Wait,
you do show affection, right?
You've been married for about…
Three years.
You're practically newlyweds. So why?
You know, time sure does fly.
It feels like I got married yesterday,
but it's already been ten years.
Time flies by so quickly,
what's the use of saving it?
When she's by your side,
tell her you love her
and thank her
as much as you can.
We've unpacked and warmed up now.
Thank you for the lunchboxes, Mr. Paik!
Thank you.
Now that we're full,
shall we start the sports competition?
Gosh.
Someone stop Mr. Kang.
Yeah. Who knew he was so into events?
All events will be played in pairs.
The teams will be
the spokespersons versus the interpreters.
Let's team up, Hee-joo.
No.
We came to build a rapport
with the interpreters.
What's the point of this retreat
if you arrange the teams like that?
Shall we mix them, perhaps?
Mr. Paik, why don't you pick
one of the interpreters first…
Okay.
Let's team up, Ms. Hong.
Then, that's one team!
- Good luck.
- Everyone else can team up too.
What's the prize?
- The winning team--
- Let them pick.
- Excuse me?
- The winning team can pick their prize.
Let's start.
What they want!
Warm up.
The first event is just a warm-up.
We'll start with
a two-person jump rope challenge!
Now.
There's a lot of room for mistakes
in this event, so you'll get two chances.
We'll start with Park Do-jae
and Kim Tae-kyeong.
- Okay, spin it.
- Good luck.
Here I go.
That was good.
That's good!
Nice!
I'll go in first.
Make sure to time it right and jump.
Speed, reflexes, timing, and focus
are all important.
Mr. Park, you look so calm.
Seven, eight!
That's too bad.
How many?
That makes it seven.
- Now, next.
- Good job.
Okay, next.
Mr. Paik's team.
Come on.
One.
Are you okay?
- Take it easy.
- That's zero.
Mr. Paik, you're out!
I'm sorry.
Once again. Next.
It's smooth this time.
Now.
I've figured out the trick.
I can do a good job this time.
Once I find the rhythm after a few jumps,
then you can--
Are you listening?
I'll go first. Just follow me.
Twelve.
How many was that?
- It's 12 this time.
- Okay.
Okay, let's get Mr. Paik's team.
Team Paik?
- Now!
- There you go! Okay!
- You have to go.
- Go, Mr. Paik!
We'll count once Mr. Paik comes in.
We finally found one.
The victim's family.
If his little brother is alive
and if he was looking for his brother,
then he may know something.
I know.
But…
it won't be easy to figure out
where he is or how he's living.
Well, the director said that
the old documents were lost or discarded
when the operating foundation changed.
Well, for now,
I'll ask the kids from the orphanage
I can get in touch with.
That's a great idea.
It's the finals for the three-legged race.
Mr. Paik and Hong Hee-joo
versus Jeong Won-bin and Ahn Jin-hee.
Who will be the winning team?
And they're off! Team Paik!
They're running neck-and-neck!
- Be careful!
- Go, Mr. Paik!
Anyone, just win!
- Good luck!
- That's a three-legged race!
Won-bin's team is slowing down!
The finish line is just ahead!
And they're down! Team Paik!
Team Paik wins!
Paik Sa-eon! Hong Hee-joo!
- Paik Sa-eon! Hong Hee-joo!
- Paik Sa-eon!
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
Okay.
Anyway, congrats!
What prize should we prepare
for the winning team?
Tell me if you want something.
There is something I want.
The weather's nice. The angle's nice.
And the models…
Did you two fight already?
Can you move closer together?
Yes, that's good.
But is one photo really enough?
I mean, it's your first place prize.
There's meat and rice.
I don't need it.
A souvenir photo will be enough.
Okay, then.
Now.
Smile.
Bigger!
That's good.
Now… Tilt your head.
Tilt. No, towards the middle, Mr. Paik.
There you go. That's good. That's perfect!
Good. Don't move.
Make a hand heart.
That's great.
Now.
I'll take it now.
Good.
Smile!
Wait.
Let's rest.
Let's rest for a little.
But you're dressed for the Himalayas.
Yeah.
Why did you want to hike this mountain?
Did I suggest it? Did I?
That man flying up there did.
Wow, well…
Can you believe Hong Hee-joo's stamina?
It's unexpected.
It's not just her stamina.
Don't those two have good chemistry?
I felt it too.
During the three-legged race,
- they were so in sync.
- Yes!
He's a married man!
You scared me!
You said it before too.
That sparks flew between the two
on the day of the interview.
- When did I?
- Goodness.
That's enough nonsense. Help me up.
Here. One, two!
Is that shirt all you have?
It's cold once the sweat dries.
Wear it later.
- Where'd you buy your hiking clothes?
- That's not the issue right now.
You dressed up the most.
Over here.
Who's the youngest among us?
Me. I am.
It's so pretty.
We're here.
It's beautiful.
Hee-joo.
Shall we take a photo together?
- Yeah.
- Sounds good.
One, two, three.
Great job, everyone.
Come and gather. Let's take a group photo.
Here's the banner.
Hold that up.
Rows of two?
Okay, behind.
Don't push in the back.
You'll be gone for good
if you fall, got it?
Now.
Okay, that's good. Gather together.
Get closer.
- Closer.
- Okay, that's good.
Look at that.
Isn't that Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon?
- That's right.
- It is him!
- Let us take a photo.
- You're so handsome!
Just a moment.
- Can we take a photo with you?
- After ours.
Wait a moment.
Just a moment. Please, don't push.
Please maintain order.
Just a moment.
Mr. Park.
People, please don't push. Maintain order.
Mr. Park! Mr. Paik!
Excuse me!
Oh, no!
- What do we do?
- What is it?
A person fell.
- Who?
- Hong Hee-joo.
It happened in the blink of an eye.
Down the cliff.
Step back. Please, step back.
Hong Hee-joo.
Hong Hee-joo!
We were just about to take a group photo,
and some hikers approached us.
They barged in and started pushing.
First, deploy the rescue team.
It's almost 6 p.m.
It'll be bad if it gets dark.
Mr. Paik!
How did he come from there?
He went down before you got here.
- Down there?
- Are you okay? Were you hurt?
How could you go down there like that?
I saw a broken tree.
I think she hit that on her way down.
Can we deploy the rescue dogs right away?
Yes, but we don't have
the missing person's belongings.
They can smell this.
She has my jacket around her waist. Hurry.
Did you get through?
No, I can't get through.
HONG HEE-JOO
The number you have dialed is…
Mr. Paik. Over here.
People, please don't push. Maintain order.
Someone…
Sis?
Do you know what kind of phone this is?
This…
can only call Paik Sa-eon.
That was really true?
Why is he so meticulous?
Hong Hee-joo!
PARK DO-JAE
- What happened?
- They're still searching.
They're searching up to 300 meters
downstream of the cliff, but…
NBN KANG TAE-KYEONG
Reporters keep calling me.
Has it already spread to the media?
I'll regulate it.
And I'll expand the search radius.
What about the security footage?
The police are checking the footage
near the trail and summit.
Our team members and people,
who were nearby when it happened,
- are being questioned as witnesses.
- If you find anything,
call me right away.
CHUGYEONG DAILY NEWS PARK GUK-JIN
Are you going to get that?
No, I'm not.
Because there's a call I'm waiting for.
Are they conducting a search?
Why don't I hear anything?
Shouldn't there be helicopters
and drones looking for me?
Is this how I'll get caught?
I'm being punished.
I should've confessed earlier.
Yeah, it's for the best.
I'll finally say it to him now.
Yeah.
He might not pick up.
No.
It's over if he doesn't.
I need to snap out of it!
Get it together.
PAIK SA-EON
Pick up. No. Don't pick up.
Pick up, please.
Hong Hee-joo!
Hee-joo.
I mean…
406.
What about Hee-joo?
How is she?
Does he think we're together?
406, can you hear me?
You said to call when there's a corpse.
That's why I called.
Come take her.
That's good.
Thank you for calling me.
Where did Hee-joo fall?
Just tell me the location.
I don't know.
406!
Listen to me carefully.
I've put a first-aid kit
inside of Hee-joo's backpack.
At the bottom of the kit,
there's a portable flare.
You can ignite it by striking the top lid.
I hope Hee-joo finds it and uses it.
What do you think, 406?
If Hee-joo wakes up,
wouldn't she try to search for something?
Are you scared?
Me?
What's there to be scared of?
I'm…
scared to death right now.
PAIK SA-EON
406!
Are you there?
Answer me!
I can hear you.
The temperature has dropped.
Do you think Hee-joo's cold?
I don't know if she's wearing my jacket.
There's water in her backpack too.
She can't get dehydrated.
She needs to drink water.
You did it.
I can see it.
Come quickly.
I'm on my way. Don't hang up!
And if you can,
please tell Hee-joo
not to worry.
Tell her I'll be right there!
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Tell me.
I'll say it once,
so listen carefully, 406.
My true feelings for Hee-joo…
What are your true feelings?
Tell me.
I can't hear you.
Hong Hee-joo.
I like you.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Starting now, I want you
to answer my questions.
The most important question.
Did you see his face?
I like it.
I like feeling your heartbeat.
Is he taking a shower? Why?
We've already slept together.
Is this real?
I felt regretful.
I don't think I've done enough for you.
No, I mean just me!
You should return my phone.
I'm on my way. Open the door.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce